University of Connecticut
© 2004 University of Connecticut
University of Connecticut, University Senate Commission on University Governance Records.
undated, 1968-1972.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Commission on University Governance.
1 linear foot.
MSS19980242
In 1971, a Commission was established to investigate proposals for University governance and report back to the University community. Dr. Albert Cohen chaired the Commission.
History
In 1971, a Commission was established to investigate proposals for University governance and report back to the University community. Dr. Albert Cohen chaired the Commission.
Scope and Content
The collection contains memoranda, reports, surveys, correspondence, clippings, minutes and similar materials collected or produced by the Commission in its work.
Arrangement
Series I: Commission Records ( undated, 1968-1972 ) are arranged alphabetically by subject.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
University of Connecticut Chronicle v. 2, #4, 7, 11, 27, 31 1971-1972.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Organizations:
University of Connecticut--Administration.
Places:
Storrs (Conn.)--Education--Universities and colleges.
Subjects:
Universities and colleges--Connecticut--Administration.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Publications.; Administrative Records.; Minutes.; Press releases.; Photocopies.; Notes.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Unknown.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Commission Records, undated, 1968-1972
  - Commission documents, undated (Box 1:, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1970-1972 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Dow incident, 1968 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Final Report of the Commission, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School, undated, 1970-1971 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Internal Commission documents
    - 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - 1972 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Legislature, 1971-1972 (Box 2:, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations and Media, 1970-1972 (Box 2:, Folder 11)
  - Supporting Materials, undated (Box 2:, Folder 12-14)
  - University of New Hampshire, 1969-1971 (Box 2:, Folder 15)